PRASHANT RAJPUT

ACCOUNTS RECEIVABLE

Ahmedabad, IN prajput7043@gmail.com +91 70437 99268 in /prashant-rajput-a6234b188

PROFILE

Responsible for conducting research and addressing claim-related issues in order to maximise provider profits. In addition, I examine claims to ensure that payer-specific billing standards are met, monitor billing, and decide and amend accounts as required.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Account Receivable Executive

05/2021 - present

iFedora Solutions Pvt. Ltd ≥

- Used highly effective oral and written communication skills in order to communicate effectively with clinicians, patients and insurance companies.
- Handled medical billing and claims resolution of commercial insurance companies, including Medicare and Medicaid replacement plans.
- Manage A/R accounts by ensuring accurate and timely follow-up.
- Understand the client requirements and specifications of the project.
- Ensure that the deliverable to the client adhere to the quality standards.

Business Analyst 04/2019 – 02/2020

Reddito Capital

- Providing financial guidance to individual investors, brokers, and investment consultants.
- Responsible for Business development through acquisition and retention of clients.
- Understanding customer requirements and providing best equaled services.
- Implementing a comprehensive management plan for each client and hold regular stakeholder meetings to keep all interested parties updated in project progress.

SKILLS

- Medicaid
- Medicare
- A/R process
- CPT and ICD-10 codes

EDUCATION

Master of CommerceO7/2018 - 04/2020

Gujarat University
INDIA

• Focused on the systematic study of the concepts in the specialized subjects and topics related to the fields of Accounting and Finance.

Bachelor of CommerceO7/2015 - 04/2018

Gujarat University
INDIA

• A degree programme with core subjects such as commerce, accounting, business studies, management, corporate finance and more combined with a specialization in accounting and management.

DECLARATION

I solemnly declare that the information in this resume is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Prashant Rajput